We will now commence the final
match of the rookie bracket!
I will be winning this.
No, I will.
Then, let's settle this!
Let's!
I will... never lose!
Ogre Scintilla!
Amelia!
Get up!
Prima materia encoding
material code decoding
material code processing
αiτία hū́lē eîdos
efficient télos embodiment
Causality.
Butterfly Effect.
Huh? Wha?
W-Wait a second!
Ariane, I told you.
You can no longer reach me.
Hey, Ray, what's going on there?
That's...
That's probably a concept
interference original.
A concept type?!
I believe it takes its source from chaos
theory's butterfly effect.
Very special sorcery that barely
anyone in this world can use.
Manipulating causality...
Interfering with causal relationships
that were supposed to occur,
making them collapse,
then tying them to other causalities,
thus overwriting them...
That's why, no matter how hard Ariane tries,
her attacks won't hit Amelia.
Um, so does that mean that
Amelia is invincible right now?
Hm, I'm not sure about that one.
Ariane, let's call it quits.
No...
I... I will never lose!
Butterfly Effect!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 9
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Releases the Binds
Father! My sister!
Ariane...
Yeah!
You got this, Amelia!
This is quite taxing for Amelia's engram.
She's definitely
close to overheating.
Huh?!
Amelia!
I will... never... lose!
Neither will I!
Ariane!
Sister!
Amelia!
Keep fighting, Amelia!
Ariane!
Ariane...
Amelia...
Your face looks terrible.
Your body is covered in burns, too.
The same goes for you, too, Ariane.
You're right.
Hey, Amelia.
Yes?
You've... gotten very strong.
Yes.
I... I've gotten strong!
It's really amazing.
Yes... Yes!
Why are you crying?
You defeated me, you know?
You know you can be proud, right?
I only got this far because
of everyone's help.
The friends I made at school...
And Ray helped me so much.
But you know...
the reason I was able to become strong
was because of you, Ariane.
Because you were always there,
ahead of me, I was able to make it this far.
So... thank you.
Thank you, too.
I was only able to pursue
being a proud aristocrat
so that I could become an example for you.
Huh?
I knew you had doubts.
Doubts about how aristocrats should be,
how you should be.
But I didn't know how to
talk to you about that.
That's why I decided that I'd always be
someone that you wouldn't be ashamed of.
Amelia, I'm so sorry.
Amelia.
We will always be friends.
Yes.
Always, always.
Always, always, always.
Ariane!
I brought everything I had into this fight.
And I lost.
Congratulations, Amelia!
You are the champion!
Thank you... Ariane!
Th-The match is over!
The champion of the rookie
bracket is Amelia Rose!
That was an amazing battle!
Both of you were really cool!
That's true!
Dear audience,
please give both of them a huge hand for
fighting it out valiantly until the end!
Yay!
You did great, Amelia!
They were so cool!
Yes!
Uncle Claude!
Uncle!
Oh, it's you, Tiana.
Hey, Claude!
Amelia was amazing.
She's not there yet.
Sheesh, just be happy for once.
She lost this time,
but Ariane is going to get even stronger.
Yeah!
Then, Amelia will get even stronger...
How great is it to have a
childhood friend and rival!
Hmph.
Ray!
Amelia, how are you feeling?
I'm fine now.
Well, I guess I look like this.
You'll recover soon.
Yeah.
Now that it's over, it feels
like it was just a flash.
There were some rough parts,
but I didn't hate it all.
I want to keep living, next to you.
No, I mean, I know!
That you meant that as
a friend, but still...
What happened?
Nothing!
By the way, did you know what my power was?
No, not in detail.
But during our training,
I did feel that you have tremendous talent.
Oh, I see.
Talent may be hereditary,
but today's fight was—
Because I tried so hard...
Right?
Of course.
Original spells are not something you just
happen to attain without any effort.
It was the proof that you've
been working hard for a long time.
Congratulations.
Once again, from the bottom of my heart.
Thank you, Ray!
Truly, thank you, thank you so mu—
If I hadn't met Ray,
I think I'd still be that bird in a cage.
Limiting myself instead of really giving it my all,
and whining with my head down.
I had forgotten for so long that there's an
endless blue sky, if you just lift your head.
Amelia!
Yes! Coming!
Today's finally the final
of the main bracket!
Let's cheer hard for Rebecca, as well.
Yeah!
I, Amelia Rose,
am no longer a bird trapped
in the cage of nobility.
I am going to live in this whole
wide world, alongside everybody else!
It's finally time for the climax
of the Magic Chevalier!
The favorite for the title
of champion is Lady Rebecca...
I mean, Rebecca Bradley.
Facing her will be the dark horse who
quickly rushed up the ranks, Lucas Forst!
That's...
Who will the goddess of victory be
smiling upon in this final match?!
I look forward to our fight.
The fight is on!
Eighth Secret Technique.
Afterglow Blackout.
Thank you.
It-It's over!
It took just a moment.
The champion of the main bracket of
the Magic Chevalier is Lucas Forst!
The dark horse of this tournament
has finally claimed the top title!
Everybody, please give him a huge hand!
You're the current Iceblade, right?
I didn't know the "Peerless Blade Sorcerer"
title had also been passed down.
You could tell?
How could I not, after seeing
that secret technique.
I figured.
I thought you might.
Why?
I don't see what reason the
"Peerless Blade Sorcerer"
has for competing in the Magic Chevalier,
which is a tournament for students.
I wanted to show you.
I want to fight against the Iceblade.
I wanted you to see that the strongest
sorcerer is the Peerless Blade.
But first, please fully cure your overheat.
Otherwise I can't fight you
with my full strength.
See you next year.
I'll be waiting here.
Next year, huh...?
Ah, man.
So the tournament's already
coming to an end.
That's kinda sad.
It was just too fast.
This Dumbpink is so annoying.
I can't believe you actually hired her!
Oh, yowch!
Lydia, you're always so mean.
But I know that you actually love me!
You're such a tsundere!
Abbie, seriously, can I hurt her?
Control yourself, Lydia.
Now's really not the time for that.
Yeah, yeah.
Do it, please.
You betcha!
Listen up!
Everything's going to be fine soon!
Baddies, look here!
Let's get going!
Carol in Wonderland!
Pew pew!
Turn right!
Turn left!
Now spin!
Jump to the left!
Step to the right!
Hands to your hips!
Close your knees and shake those hips!
She really is the
"Spellbinding Sorcerer", huh?
Shake, shake, shake.
It's in such poor taste.
And one more time!
Dumbpink! Stop playing and do it already!
All right!
Now, let's get to it.
Spit out everything about your
bosses and your future plans!
Come on, release all
of your pubescent worries!
Ow...
So this is how the Empire does it, huh?
Despicable.
That's in bad taste!
It's the closing ceremony of
the Magic Chevalier tournament
and all the contestants have gathered here!
They are being showered
by relentless applause
for having endured four
days of intense fighting!
Congratulations, Amelia!
Congrats!
Phew, I made it!
Miss Carol, where have you been?!
A girl's got secrets!
Right... And who's that next to you?
Don't worry about me.
Just a beautiful girl, passing through.
Wha?
Dina, your next line!
Oh, and now the closing speech from the
chair of the tournament organizers,
the principal of the Arnold Academy
of Sorcery, Abbie Garnet!
This year's Magic Chevalier has
concluded safely!
While you are all students,
all of you showed us battles
on an extremely high level.
And many thanks to our audience and our
staff for cheering everybody on, as well.
I look forward to seeing you here
in this arena again next year!
That is all!
For this year's cultural festival,
I suggest that our class should be run
a maid cafe!
What is the meaning of this?!
Why do we have to pretend to be servants?!
We're nobles!
A cafe with maids?!
And the maids serve tea?
I mean, probably.
I can't be a maid!
Classes and clubs need to get approval
to be in the cultural festival.
So to begin with,
we need to get consent during
tomorrow's class vote.
Hm, I got the gist of it.
But what, exactly, is it that you want do so
badly that you're willing to be an organizer?
This.
A maid cafe?
This is an excellent proposal.
Wouldn't this garner everyone's
support if you just submitted this?
We have a lot of highborn
girls in our class, right?
Do you think they would
willingly become maids?
Now that you mention it...
Just suggesting this won't work.
That's why I wanted to ask for your help.
But how am I, as a guy, going to—
Ray! Listen!
Yes?
In the face of the wonderfulness of maids,
male or female... none of that matters!
Maids!
Their existence alone is
already so attractive!
When you think that they are always
just loyal to their master,
sometimes they have the captivating
expression of a goddess!
And that uniform is splendid, as well!
While it isn't flashy,
there is a modest, yet noble, beauty there!
Oh...
That's true!
Certainly not someone
to look down on!
Maid in heaven!
Welcome to my destiny!
You get it, right?! Right?!
Yeah!
My suggestion is that the maid outfit at the
cultural festival will have a shorter skirt!
It's a departure from the standard,
but I think it will be ideal for
a casual foray into maiddom!
The length of the skirt makes a difference?
Yes! Of course it does!
Actually,
we ought to be pushing to make
this style the standard trend!
The maids who used to live in the shadow
of their masters
are finally declaring they exist!
Don't you think that's revolutionary?!
I think that sounds really good!
Carocaro thinks you guys would
all make for very cute maids!
Behold!
Tada!
I'm so glad that went well.
I hope we didn't strong-arm
them all into this.
It's fine, it's fine!
Your passionate speech was very moving.
Impressive.
If we're talking about impressive,
I think that applies to you more for having
brought Carol on board before, as well.
Ray!
Miss Sera?
Did something happen?
Rebecca... She...
Did something happen to her?
Apparently, she got "engaged"!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
This is the preview of the next episode of
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World!
The cultural festival is a can't-miss event!
Everyone comes together
in their love of elegant frills.
They say that this outfit is so
attractive that nobody can resist.
"The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Sets Up a Maid Cafe"!
Episode 10
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Sets Up a Maid Cafe
This has been Ariane Algren.